<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Project Z1</string>
    <string name="app_intro_title">Choose Your Own Adventure</string>
    <string name="choose_your_own_adventure">Choose Your Own Adventure</string>

    <string name="loading_1">Assets Loading</string>
    <string name="loading_2">Level Compiling</string>
    <string name="loading_3">Data Collecting</string>
    <string name="loading_4">Challenges Creating</string>

    <string name="start_game">Start</string>
    <!--Note: Eventually, replace buttons with clickable icons-->

    <!--Strings for level names-->
    <string name="level_1_name">Level 1: Forest</string>
    <string name="level_2_name">Level 2: Hotel</string>
    <string name="level_3_name">Level 3: Army Bunker</string>
    <string name="level_4_name">Level 4: Underwater</string>
    <string name="level_5_name">Level 5: Mines</string>

    <!--Strings for level 1 scenes-->
    <string name="level_1_advice_1">Be cautious…the decisions are by no means easy.</string>
    <string name="level_1_advice_2">Beware those who are treacherous, my champion. Soon you will rise to greatness.</string>
    <string name="level_1_advice_3">The easy decision isn\'t always the best. Look in the long term</string>
    <string name="level_1_advice_4">You are but a playing piece in a larger game</string>
    <string name="level_1_advice_end">Your journey will start now.</string>


    <string name="health_describer">Health: </string>
    <string name="health">100</string>
    <string name="score_describer">Score: </string>
    <string name="score">0</string>

    <!--Tier 1 scenario + buttons -->
    <string name="starting_scenario">You are taking a hike in the forest.\n\n
                                     You have enough food, water and supplies for one day.\n\n
                                     It gets dark, so you turn on your flashlight.\n\n
                                     After a couple of hours, your battery dies and you don\'t have a spare.\n\n
                                     You mentally curse yourself for not being prepared.\n\n
                                     You realize that you can\'t keep walking in the dark, and your supplies are running low,
                                     so you have two options: \n\n
                                     Go find shelter or go find water</string>

    <string name="find_shelter">Find Shelter</string>
    <string name="find_water">Find Water</string>


    <!--Tier 2 scenarios + buttons -->
    <string name="shelter_scenario">
                You try to find shelter. Eventually, you spot a cave. \n\n
                Its not the best, but it has to work for now. \n\n
                You unpack your remaining supplies, and try to get comfortable, but
                just when you are about to  go to sleep, you spot something odd on the ground. \n\n
                On closer inspection, its not so odd..just pawprints…  \n\n
                …PAWPRINTS?!? \n\n
                You get really scared that this may be the home of a large predator....like a bear. \n\n
                Fortunately for you, the footprints appear to be fairly old ...like a few days ago \n\n
                You\'re extremely exhausted, but you\'re worried about the bear too. \n\n
                What do you do: Stay and rest, or leave the cave and try to find a safer place to sleep</string>

    <string name="stay_and_rest">Stay</string>
    <string name="leave_the_cave">Leave</string>


    <string name="water_scenario">You go and try to find some water. \n\n
                                 Before long, you see a stream. \n\n
                                 There are fish swimming slowly in the stream. \n\n
                                 Do you: Try to catch some fish or get some water</string>

    <string name="try_to_catch_fish">Catch fish</string>
    <string name="get_some_water">Get water</string>


    <!--Tier 3 scenarios + buttons -->
        <!--Tier 3a: shelter origin scenarios + buttons -->
    <string name="stay_in_cave"> You decide to stay. \n\n
                                You are extremely uneasy about the bear, but eventually you fall asleep. \n\n
                                <!--(Day 2 )(+ 5 health) split into two strings?-->
                                You wake up  in the morning to the sound of soft growling....oh no \n\n
                                You open your eyes and you see a bear a short distance away from you in the cave. \n\n
                                You have two options: Either try to make a run for it, or play dead</string>

    <string name="run_from_cave">Run</string>
    <string name="play_dead">Play Dead</string>


    <string name="leave_cave">You decide to stay on the safe side and find a safer place to sleep \n\n
                                You get more and more tired. \n\n
                                <!-- -20 health -->
                                Eventually, you see a hut in the distance, and you walk towards it slowly, your steps getting weaker and weaker. \n\n
                                Do you try to get to the hut, or do you give in to your tiredness and sleep </string>

    <string name="try_get_to_hut">Get to Hut</string>
    <string name="sleep">Sleep</string>

        <!--Tier 3b: water origin scenarios + buttons -->

    <string name="catch_some_fish"> You try to catch some fish and manage to grab a good sized fish and cook it over a fire you made. \n\n
                                The fish tasted quite good.
                                Feeling full, and quite tired by the end of the day, you fall asleep in your sleeping bag \n\n

          <!--  —Line 2—
            -Day 2- +5 Health -->

            <!--(-20 health) -->
                            You wake up to a big stomachache. \n\n
                            It turns out the river was polluted, and the fish had absorbed some of the toxins. \n\n
                            Luckily for you, the fish you caught swam there from a different river. \n\n
                            Also, you cooked the fish, which eliminated some of the toxins. \n\n
                            You still don\'t want to take your chances with the water, so you try to find another stream once you recover from the stomachache. \n\n</string>

    <string name="catch_some_fish_p2">  On the way to the stream, you see a medium sized snake by your foot. You remember this snake from a book you read once, and realize that it is venomous. \n\n
                            You back up slowly, knowing that is the best way to avoid getting bitten, but you back up into a ruined wall. You now can only move forwards or to the sides \n\n
                            Do you: Run away as fast as you can, hoping you can outrun the snake, or do you stay absolutely still:</string>

    <string name="run_away">Run Away</string>
    <string name="stay_still">Stay Still</string>


    <string name="drink_water">You are extremely thirsty and decide to take some water. \n\n
                                The water seems clear, and fish are swimming lazily in the river. \n\n
                                If you boil the water, you lose much of the water to steam, and you have to put more effort in, making you even more tired. \n\n
                                If you drink the water plain, you might risk getting sick, but you won' t invest too much energy \n\n
                                Do you: Boil the water or drink it plain? </string>

    <string name="boil_water">Boil Water</string>
    <string name="drink_plain">Drink Plain</string>

    <!--Tier 4 scenarios + buttons -->



</resources>